1. appUnderTest = resolveAppPath(appFileName)
1. configuredValue = configuredAppFileName.toString()
5. if (!(configuredValue))
9. configuredFile = new java.io.File(configuredValue)
13. if (configuredFile.isAbsolute() && configuredFile.exists())
17. candidateFileNames = [configuredValue]
21. if (!(candidateFileNames.contains("Katalian.Banking (1).apk")))
1. candidateFileNames.add("Katalian.Banking (1).apk")
25. projectDir = new java.io.File(com.kms.katalon.core.configuration.RunConfiguration.getProjectDir())
29. apkFile = findFirstFileByName(projectDir, candidateFileNames)
1. matchingFile = null
5. rootDir.eachFileRecurse()
9. return matchingFile
33. if (apkFile == null)
1. throw new java.io.FileNotFoundException(Unable to locate Android APK using candidates $candidateFileNames under project directory '$projectDir.absolutePath'.)
1. println(testCaseContext.getTestCaseId())
5. println(testCaseContext.getTestCaseStatus())